Guide to the Evelyn Rich Papers, 1956-1993 RL.11363
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Far Right Groups, 3
  - Notes, Printed Material, Ephemera
    - The Truth, issue 1, London, AR, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - SS Action Group ephemera, Dearborn Heights, MI, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Institute for Historical Review flyers, ephemera, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Institute for Historical Review: Notes from a visit to IHR Conference with David Duke, and visit to Las Vegas, undated; 18 pages (Box 2, Folder 71)
      Includes 2 photographs.
    - Robert E. Miles: 33/5 Klan manual, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Mountain Church, Cohoctah, MI: From the Mountain newsletter, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Mountain Church: Free Association Forum agenda, 1986 Apr. 19-20 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      Recording CS-0013.
    - Robert E. Miles: Report of a visit by Evelyn Rich to Miles's place (Cohoctah, MI) and later road trip with Don Black, undated; 7 pages (Box 2, Folder 75)
      Presumably from her visit to the Free Association Forum, 1986. Recording CS-0013.
    - Free Association Forum (Bob Miles's place) and Don Black: photographs and negatives, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - National Association for the Advancement of White People (NAAWP): NAAWP News, 1980-1988; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 77-78)
    - David Duke political campaigns: literature, mailings, ephemera, poster, 1988-1993; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 79-80)
      Assorted items from Duke's run for Senate, LA Governor, and the US Presidency.
    - David Duke presidential campaign announcement photographs, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - David Duke presidential campaign New Hampshire primary photographs, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - David Duke clippings re: political career, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 83)
      Includes clippings re: Rich's recordings and her media interviews.
    - Assorted white power/Nazi ephemera, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - "Chapter One" of unidentified manuscript, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Audio Resources
    - David Duke interviewed by Tom Snyder on Tomorrow Show, 1974; 00:56:06
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0032)
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0042)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0032_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (starting at 00:14:55) (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0042.WAV)
    - Leonard Zakim Boston ADL & Joe Feaster Boston NAACP Discuss KKK on Gene Burns Programme March 1981, 1981-03; 00:51:47
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0003)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0003_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0003_02.WAV)
    - David Duke on the Bob Grant Show, WABC, circa 1985; 01:09:28
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0012)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0012_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0012_02.WAV)
    - Klan Rally, Feb 24, 1985 Raleigh, NC, 1985-02-24; 00:41:36
      - Original audiocassette, side 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0031)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0031_02.WAV)
    - Telephone calls to Robert Shelton, Stanley McCollum, Dannie Hawkins, Professor David Chalmers, Richmond Flowers, Roger Handley, 1985-07; 00:43:57
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0035)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0035_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0035_02.WAV)
    - White Patriot Party Rally, Jasper, Georgia, 1985-07-13; 00:46:28
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0010)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0010_01.WAV)
    - White Patriot Party Rally, Kennesaw, Georgia, 1985-08-03; 00:15:53
      - Original audiocassette, side 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0029)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0029_02.WAV)
    - Identity Church, Los Angeles, CA, 1986; 01:21:32
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0045)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0045_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0045_02.WAV)
    - Free Association Forum, Cohoctah, MI, 1986-04-19/1986-04-20; 02:43:08
      Tapes 1 and 3 only.
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0024)
        "Tape 1: Col. James Buford, 'Report from Chicago,' Edward Melkonian, 'Report from Illinois,' Thom Robb, 'Christians Awake,' Pastor John Gerhardt, 'Stay out of the argument,' Robert Miles, Craig Mackenzie, 'The Kondratieff Wave.'"
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0025)
        "Tape 3: Capt. Boone, 'Keystone News,' Robert Miles, Maj. D.V. Clerkin, 'The Talon Report,' Robert Miles, Don Black, 'Red Clay and Political Hay,' Robert Miles, Pastor Robert Strittmatter, 'Why the Northwest,' Robert Miles, Glen Miller."
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0024_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0024_02.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 3 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0025_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 4 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0025_02.WAV)
    - David Duke, WRKO radio interview, Boston, MA, 1987; 00:46:06
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0026)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0026.WAV)
    - David Duke; Core; New Amsterdam News Editor; Howard Beach Discussion, 1987-02; 01:00:42
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0033)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0033_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0033_02.WAV)
    - Daniel Johnson & Tom Metzger WRKO Radio "Ted & Janet Show," Cairo, IL, 1987-07-01; 00:49:05
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0021)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0021.WAV)
    - "20/20" ABC TV. "Klan Murder", 1987-07-09; 00:19:39
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0043)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0043.WAV)
    - David Duke w/David Brudnoy WBZ-AM, Boston, MA, 1987-12-02; 01:26:46
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0002)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0002_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0002_02.WAV)
    - David Duke's announcement for presidential run, and press conference, Marriott Hotel, Atlanta, GA, 1988; 01:21:24
      - Original audiocassette, sides 1 and 2 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0039)
      - Digital audio file, part 1 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0039_01.WAV)
      - Digital audio file, part 2 (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0039_02.WAV)
    - David Duke on KCBS, 1991; 00:08:04
      Evelyn Rich interview with Joe Fields and David Duke, from 1986, used for KCBS radio story on David Duke
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0014)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0014.WAV)
    - Daniel Carver on the Howard Stern Show, circa 1993; 00:44:44
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0044)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0044.WAV)
    - "The People's Party," song by Clarence H. Johnson, undated; 00:07:27
      - Original audiocassette, side 1 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11363-CS-0046)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11363-SET-0001, Object RL11363-CS-0046.WAV)